PETER MULIKOV

FRONT-END-DEVELOPER

I'm JavaScript / React.js developer, team-player with a strong motivation, desire, and ability to learn. I perform the tasks entrusted to me efficiently and independently.

My goal is to become a highly qualified Full-Stack (MERN) developer. I want to be helpful to the team and take part in creating incredible projects.

My intention is to constantly learn, gain new knowledge and experience, and improve my abilities.



Krakow, Poland



+48-518-409-445



pettergov1@gmail.com



github.com/mulikov-peter



www.linkedin.com/in/petermulikov

SKILLS

- ✓ HTML
- ✓ CSS / SASS
- ✓ JavaScript OOP/ES6+
- ✓ React.js / Hooks
- ✓ Git
- ✓ Bootstrap

LEARNING

- ✓ Node.js / Express.js
- ✓ Mongo DB
- ✓ TypeScript
- ✓ Redux

LANGUAGES

- ✓ Ukrainian /Russian native
- ✓ Polish upper-intermediate
- ✓ English intermediate
- ✓ Spanish basic

INTERESTS

Programming, Football, Crossfit, Moto-Gp, Cooking, Traveling

MY PROJECTS

- Map of self-service repair stations. Real-world application with map of self-service repair points for bicycles (only for Cracow).
- Recipes. Rest API application for searching recipes.
- Guess Country. The game for guessing country by flag. Info about country comes from Rest API.
- Cocktails. Rest API application for searching cocktails.

You are welcome to my <u>GitHub</u> for checking all my projects.

EDUCATION

2003 – 2008: S.K. Kharkiv National University of Economics. Economics, master's degree.

2008 – 2014: V.N. Karazin Kharkiv National University. Law, bachelor's degree.

EXPERIENCE

09.2021 – present: Freelance - Front-End developer.

03.2016 – 09.2021: Nic Nowego Ltd. – Sous chef.

11.2012 – 02.2016: AD Forvard Ltd. – Selling manager.

10.2009 – 11.2012: Tax inspection – Police officer.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).